# **Mojgan Moradi**Architecture Designer



- Tehran, Iran
- ™ mojganmoradi707@gmail.com
- **\** +989120599588
- in linkedin.com/in/mojganmoradi
- k https://mojganmoradi.com

## **About Me**

a graduate of architectural engineering, who is currently working in my own architectural office. Interested in sustainable architecture with more than 10 years of work experience in the fields of interior and exterior architecture, exhibition and furniture design, green roofs and green spaces, urban and neighborhood design, etc. Proficient in relevant software and interested in team work. I believe that all spaces can be beautiful and functional if there are creative ideas behind them.

# <u>Skills</u>

AutoCAD Lumion

V-Ray For 3D Max

Autodesk 3ds Max

Corel DRAW

Adobe Photoshop

SketchUp Revit

Corona Renderer

Grasshopper •

## Languages

**persian** *Natuve* 

English
TOEFL 105

## **Professional Experience**

## Founder Ramko Office, Architecture Engineering, Ramko Office ☑

Feb 2016 - present | Tehran, Iran

The company specializes in offering comprehensive services encompassing the design, construction, and supervision of commercial, office, residential, and landscape complexes. These services include designing, facade design, supervision of facade construction, landscape design, designing of villas and residential apartments, office and commercial building design, roof garden design, as well as supervision of construction of green spaces and ongoing projects.

## **Senior Design Architect,** Omranveys company

Nov 2015 - Dec 2016 | Tehran, Iran

The scope of services offered includes the design of luxury projects, facade design, supervision of facade construction, landscape design, design of villas and residential apartments, office and commercial building design, roof garden design, as well as supervision of construction of green spaces.

#### Senior Design Architect, Darkoobtalaei

Nov 2014 - Oct 2015 | Tehran, Iran

The range of services offered by the company includes the design of international exhibition stands, the interior design of office companies, executive plan design, international exhibition poster and billboard design, main exhibition plan design, supervision of exhibition construction, as well as selection and procurement of necessary materials.

#### **Exhibition and interior designer,** *Maxdesigngroup*

Aug 2013 - Jan 2014 | Tehran, Iran

The company offers a wide array of design services that include designing international exhibition stands, interior design for office companies, designing executive plans, international exhibition posters and billboard designs, and designing the main plan of exhibitions.

## **Assistant Designer,** *Tehran Beautification org* ☑

Jul 2011 - Jul 2013 | Tehran, Iran

As an assistant designer, I performed various tasks such as editing plans, calculating parking requirements, preparing reports, estimating dilapidated neighborhoods, and presenting alternative solutions for beautifying and renovating such areas in Tehran.

## **Education**

#### Master of Architecture - MArch/Architectural Engineering,

Islamic Azad University North Tehran Branch (Grade 4.6/5) 2016 – 2018 | Tehran, Iran

2010 - 2016 | Terrian, Itali

## Bachelor of Architecture - BArch/Architectural Engineering,

Natural Disasters Research Institute (NDRI) ( Grade 4.29/5 )

2013 - 2015 | Tehran, Iran

# Associate of Architecture -AArch/Architectural Engineering,

University of applied science, culture and art of Tehran municipality (Grade 4.42/5) 2010 – 2012 | Tehran, Iran

# **Publications**

"Exploring the Hidden Layers of the Eventful and Responsive City of Sanandaj with Emphasis on the Pedestrian Urban Perspective", presented at the International Conference on Applied Research in Civil Engineering, Architecture, and Urban Planning, Munich, Germany, July 2023.

"The Spatial Organization of Sanandaj's Historical Fabric: A Sustainable Model for the Survival of the City's Soul (A Study of the Historical Fabric of Khosroabad)", presented at the 2nd International Conference of Iranian Architecture and Urbanism Students, Tehran, Iran, July 2023.

"Nexor Structures: A Revolutionary Approach to Modular Building Systems", presented at the 5th International Conference and 6th National Conference on Civil Engineering, Architecture, Art, and Urban Design, Tabriz, Iran, July 2023.

"The Impact of Nexor Structures on Contemporary Architecture and Urban Planning: Benefits, Limitations, and Future Opportunities", presented at the 10th Conference on Modern Studies and Research in Civil Engineering, Architecture, and Future Cities, Tehran, Iran, May 2023.

"Exploring the Effect of Nexor Structures on Zero-Energy Architecture: A Review of Design Principles and Sustainable Strategies", presented at the same International Conference on Modern Studies in Civil Engineering, Architecture, Urban Planning, and the Environment in the 21st Century, Tehran, Iran, July 2023.

#### References

**Dr. Amir Masoud Dabagh**, Associate professor & Faculty Member at Soore University dabagh@soore.ac.ir

## Dr. Ahmad Mirza Koochak Khoshnevis,

Associate professor & Faculty Member at Research Institute of Cultural Heritage & Tourism's a.khoshnevis@richt.ir